Recently
Health Biotech
for illegal production
and tax evasion
Rep Zoe got one year
Others with minor involvement
were detained for 15 days
Lewes
Why did you bring us here
I bought this place
To produce our own feed
Dad will be the manager
in charge of production
Me, the manager
I don't know anything about it
I'll teach you
The equipment is ready
I'll provide the tech
You just keep watch
Make sure there are no slips
Mom, you have a big mission
Your mom knows nothing either
Our life is finally improving
Cynthia and I want a baby
You'll look after the grandchild
Really? That's wonderful
I promised
I'd make you live with pride
I've finally achieved part of it
Old man, we were nobodies for years
Now no one in town can top us
Alright, alright
Stop crying, it's embarrassing